Guide to the Jeh Vincent Johnson Papers, 1917-2020 (bulk 1945-2004)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Series III. Artwork and Writing, circa 1940-2013
  - Writings - "An Outline of Personal Reactions to the Commission Hearings and Field Trips, May-October", 1967 (Folder 5.33)
  - Writings - Poetry, circa 1950s (Folder 5.34)
  - Writings - "Profile of General Practice in Architecture", 1981 Oct (Folder 5.35)
  - Writings - "Reflections", 1998 (Folder 5.36)
  - Writings - "Report from a Douglas Commissioner", 1969 (Folder 5.37)
  - Writings - Review of "Building to Last" by Herb Greene and Nanine Hilliard Greene, 1982 (Folder 5.38)
  - Writings - "Statement by Jeh V. Johnson for AIA Concerning HUD Appropriations", 1970 Apr 8 (Folder 5.39)
  - Writings - "Statement of the AIA presented by J. V. Johnson and Rai Y. Okamoto, 1969 May 7 (Folder 5.40)
  - Writings - "Statement on a Select Senate Committee on Technology and the Human Environment Before the Subcommittee on Intergovernmental Relations", 1969 May 7 (Folder 5.41)
  - Writings - "Symbolism, Excess, and Values in Housing Design", 1970 (Folder 5.42)
  - Writings - Untitled work, [1952?] (Folder 5.43)
- Series IV. Subject Files, 1953-2014
  - African-American Churches, 1992-2004 (Folders 5.44-5.45)
  - African-American Churches - Clippings and ephemera, 1998-2007 (Folder 5.46)
  - Black Architects - The American Institute of Architecture Students, "Minorities in Architecture," program, 1992 (Folder 5.47)
  - Black Architects - Articles and ephemera, 1989-1993 (Folder 5.48)
  - Black Architects - Clippings, 1985-2001 (Folder 5.49)
  - Black Architects - Correspondence, 1989-1992 (Folder 5.50)
  - Black Architects - Exhibit: "Black Involvement in Architecture", circa 1970 (Folder 5.51)
  - Black Architects - Symposium: People of Color in Architecture, 1991 (Folder 5.52)
  - Black Architects - "Thematic Study of Black Architects, Builders and Developers in Washington D. C. - Phase I", 1993 (Folder 5.53)
  - Fisk University, 1992-2014 (Folder 6.1)
  - Fisk University, clippings, 1964-2007 (Folder 6.2)
  - Fisk University, correspondence, 1997-2002 (Folder 6.3)
  - Fisk University, publications, 1991-2007 (Folder 6.4)
  - Historic American Buildings - Louisiana, 1989 (Folder 6.5)
  - Miscellaneous, clippings, 1953-2008 (Folder 6.6)
  - Miscellaneous, publications, 2006, undated (Folder 6.7)
- Series V. Vassar College, 1964-2018
  - African-American Alumnae/i of Vassar College (AAAVC) Triennial, 2018 (Folder 6.8)
  - Annual activity reports, 1966-1990 (Folder 6.9)
  - Annual activity reports, 1991-1999 (Folder 6.10)
  - Architectural Design course, 1980 (Folder 6.11)
  - Architecture majors, 1975-1998 (Folder 6.12)
  - Class enrollment, 1968-1996 (Folder 6.13)
  - Class handouts and samples, circa 1980s (Folder 6.14)
  - Class handouts and samples, 1987-2000 (Folder 6.15)
  - Convocation, 2001 (Folder 6.16)
  - Correspondence, 1968-2001 (Folder 6.17)
  - Correspondence - Huenik, Peter, 1968-1993 (Folder 6.18)
  - Course planning and schedules, 1970-1998 (Folder 6.19)
  - Course planning and schedules, 1998-2000 (Folder 6.20)
  - Course schedules, 1979-2001 (Folder 6.21)
  - Employment contracts, 1964-2000 (Folder 6.22)
  - Graduate schools in architecture for Vassar graduates, 1966-1998 (Folder 6.23)
  - Independent Program in Architecture, 1974-1982 (Folder 6.24)
  - Letter to former students, 1981 (Folder 6.25)
  - Letters to/from current and former students, 1967-1969; [RESTRICTED UNTIL 2035] (Folder 10.12)
  - Letters to/from current and former students, 1970-1975; [RESTRICTED UNTIL 2035] (Folders 10.13-10.14)
  - Letters to/from current and former students, 1976-1979; [RESTRICTED UNTIL 2035] (Folder 10.15)
  - Letters to/from current and former students, 1980-1983; [RESTRICTED UNTIL 2035] (Folder 10.16)
  - Letters to/from current and former students, 1984-1989; [RESTRICTED UNTIL 2035] (Folder 10.17)
  - Letters to/from current and former students, 1990-1995; [RESTRICTED UNTIL 2035] (Folder 10.18)
  - Letters to/from current and former students, 2000-2002; [RESTRICTED UNTIL 2035] (Folder 10.19)
  - Minority students and alumnae/i, 1982-1990 (Folder 6.26)
  - Notebook, 1975-1977 (Folder 6.27)
  - Notes and writings, 1995-2011 (Folder 6.28)
  - Notes on Vassar students, 1982-1993; [RESTRICTED UNTIL 2035] (Folder 10.20)
  - Pre-Architectural School program at Vassar, 1967-1978 (Folder 6.29)
  - Speaking invitations, 1967-1970 (Folder 6.30)
  - Teaching notes, 1966-1968, undated (Folder 6.31)
  - Urban Studies Program, circa 1966-1980 (Folder 6.32)
- Series VI. Personal and Family Papers, 1917-2015
  - Address lists, 1945-1979 (Folder 6.33)
  - Bond, Max - Memorial, 2009 (Folder 6.34)
  - Branch Family Reunions, 1990-1996 (Folder 6.35)
  - Branch Family Reunions, 2001-2002 (Folder 6.36)
  - Branch Family Reunions, 2005 (Folder 6.37)
  - Branch Family Reunions, 2007 (Folder 6.38)
  - Clifford, Patricia Johnson - Biographical information, 1950-2008 (Folder 6.39)
  - Heraldic crest (wooden), undated (Folder 6.40)
  - Johnson, Charles S. - Clippings and publications, 1946-2014 (Folder 6.41)
  - Johnson, Charles S. - Trips to India, 1917-1953 (Folder 6.42)
  - Johnson Family - Clippings, circa 1952 (Folder 6.43)
  - Johnson, Jeh C. - Appointment as head of Homeland Security, clippings, 2013-2014 (Folder 6.44)
  - Johnson, Jeh C. - Appointment as head of Homeland Security, letters of congratulations, 2013 (Folder 6.45)
  - Johnson, Jeh C. - High school commencement program (speaker), 2009 (Folder 6.46)
  - Johnson, Jeh C. - Obama administration, 2006-2009 (Folder 7.1)
  - Johnson, Jeh V. - American Arbitration Association plaque, undated (Box 13)
  - Johnson, Jeh V. - Beta Sigma Tau, 1951-1958 (Folder 7.2)
  - Johnson, Jeh V. - Bio notes and resumes, 1970-2009 (Folder 7.3)
  - Johnson, Jeh V. - Burglary incident, 1989 (Folder 7.4)
  - Johnson, Jeh V. - Calendar, 1948-1949 (Folder 7.5)
  - Johnson, Jeh V. - Certificate - Junior High School, 1946 (Folder 7.6)
  - Johnson, Jeh V. - Certificate - Rehabilitation Programs, Inc., 1982 Oct 3 (Folder 7.7)
  - Johnson, Jeh V. - Certificates and awards, 1970-2002 (Folder 7.8)
  - Johnson, Jeh V. - Certificates and awards - Eleanor Roosevelt Val-Kill Medal, 2009 (Folder 7.9)
  - Johnson, Jeh V. - Certificates and awards - National Organization of Minority Architects, 1993 Oct 9 (Folder 7.10)
  - Johnson, Jeh V. - Certificates and awards - National Organization of Minority Architects, New York Chapter, 1992 Nov 23; [wooden plaque] (Box 13)
  - Johnson, Jeh V. - Certificates and awards - New York State Board of Architecture, 1983 (Folder 7.11)
  - Johnson, Jeh V. - Certificates and awards - University of the State of New York, Education Department, license to practice architecture, 1962 Oct 23; [framed] (Box 15 (Oversize))
  - Johnson, Jeh V. - Certificates and awards - Pennsylvania State Board of Examiners of Architects, license to practice architecture, 1976 Feb 20; [framed] (Box 15 (Oversize))
  - Johnson, Jeh V. - Clipping, Southern Dutchess News, 1987 (Folder 7.12)
  - Johnson, Jeh V. - Clippings, 1982-2009 (Folder 7.13)
  - Johnson, Jeh V. - Columbia University, 1948-1952 (Folder 7.14)
  - Johnson, Jeh V. - Columbia University, Bachelor of Arts, 1953; [framed] (Box 15 (Oversize))
  - Johnson, Jeh V. - Columbia University, Master of Architecture (issued to replace Bachelor of Architecture received in 1958), 1975; [framed] (Box 15 (Oversize))
  - Johnson, Jeh V. - Columbia University, schoolwork, 1952-1953 (Folder 7.15)
  - Johnson, Jeh V. - Financial ledger, 1992-1998 (Folder 7.16)
  - Johnson, Jeh V. - Financial ledger, 1992 Apr - 1993 Aug (Folder 11.2)
  - Johnson, Jeh V. - Financial ledger, 1993 Aug - 1995 May (Folder 11.3)
  - Johnson, Jeh V. - Financial ledger, 1995 May - 1996 Dec (Folder 11.4)
  - Johnson, Jeh V. - Financial ledger, 1997 Jan - 1998 Dec (Folder 11.5)
  - Johnson, Jeh V. - Financial ledger, 1999 Jan - 2002 Feb (Folder 11.6)
  - Johnson, Jeh V. - Financial ledger, 2002 Feb - 2007 Jun (Folder 11.7)
  - Johnson, Jeh V. - Financial records, 1991-2007 (Folder 7.17)
  - Johnson, Jeh V. - Financial records, graphs and charts, 1985-2004 (Folder 7.18)
  - Johnson, Jeh V. - Financial records, miscellaneous, 1945-1955 (Folder 7.19)
  - Johnson, Jeh V. - Financial records, miscellaneous, 1971-1997 (Folder 7.20)
  - Johnson, Jeh V. - Financial statements, 1978-2001 (Folder 7.21)
  - Johnson, Jeh V. - High School, 1946-1949 (Folder 7.22)
  - Johnson, Jeh V. - High School Reunions, 1949-1982 (Folder 7.23)
  - Johnson, Jeh V. - High School Reunions, 1991-1999 (Folder 7.24)
  - Johnson, Jeh V. - High School Reunions, 2007 (Folder 7.25)
  - Johnson, Jeh V. - Kiva Club, 1967-1972 (Folder 7.26)
  - Johnson, Jeh V. - Martin Luther King, Jr. Breakfast (2000 Jan 21), 1999-2000 (Folder 7.27)
  - Johnson, Jeh V. - Miscellaneous ephemera, 1969-1998 (Folder 7.28)
  - Johnson, Jeh V. - Passports, 2003, 2013 (Folder 7.29)
  - Johnson, Jeh V. - "Records and businesses", 1944-1949 (Folder 7.30)
  - Johnson, Jeh V. - Selective Service card, 1952 (Folder 7.31)
  - Johnson, Jeh V. - Sigma Pi Phi, membership roster, 1971 Jul (Folder 7.32)
  - Johnson, Jeh V. - "Storage", 1997-2004 (Folder 7.33)
  - Johnson, Jeh V. - Travel, Martha's Vineyard, 2013-2014 (Folder 7.34)
  - Johnson, Jeh V. - Travel, mileage by trip, 1956-2008 (Folder 7.35)
  - Johnson, Jeh V. - "Travel and meetings", 1970-1993 (Folder 7.36)
  - Johnson, Jeh V. - Travel plans, 1958-2003 (Folder 7.37)
  - Johnson, Jeh V. and Norma - Hudson River Housing Award, clipping, 2011 (Folder 7.38)
  - Johnson, Norma Edelin - Alpha Kappa Alpha sorority award, 1999 (Folder 7.39)
  - Johnson, Norma Edelin - Awards programs, 1997-1998 (Folder 7.40)
  - Johnson, Norma Edelin - Certificate of appreciation, Planned Parenthood Federation of America, 1994 (Folder 7.41)
  - Johnson, Robert B. - Writings, 1956-1958 (Folder 7.42)
  - Morehouse College - 15th "A Candle in the Dark" Gala, program, 2003 (Folder 7.43)
  - Morehouse College - 15th Annual "A Candle in the Dark" Gala, poster, 2003 (Roll Box 114)
  - Obituaries - Friends and family, 1998-2015 (Folder 7.44)
- Series VII. Photographic Materials, circa 1955 - [2010?]
  - Photographs
    - Architecture Jobs, 1982-1989 (Folder 7.45)
    - Architecture Jobs, 1990-1998 (Folder 7.46)
    - Architecture Jobs, undated (Folders 7.47-7.49)
    - Architecture Jobs - Apartments, 1982, undated (Folder 7.50)
    - Architecture Jobs - Central Baptist Church, Salt Point, NY, 1989 (Folder 7.51)
    - Architecture Jobs - Churches, 1989-1997 (Folder 7.52)
    - Architecture Jobs - Dutcher House Apartments, Pawling, NY, circa 1976 (Folder 7.53)
    - Architecture Jobs - Ebenezer Baptist Church, 1997 (Folder 8.1)
    - Architecture Jobs - Greater Centennial Homes, Mount Vernon, NY, circa 1972 (Folder 8.2)
    - Architecture Jobs - Greene Avenue Senior Citizens Apartments, Brooklyn, circa 1980 (Folder 8.3)
    - Architecture Jobs - Harriet Tubman Terrace Apartments, Poughkeepsie, NY, circa 1978 (Folder 8.4)
    - Architecture Jobs - Interfaith Towers, 1974 (Folder 8.5)
    - Architecture Jobs - Kings Court Apartments, Mount Vernon, NY, circa 1977 (Folder 8.6)
    - Architecture Jobs - Lagrange Town Hall, LaGrange, NY, 1968 (Folder 8.7)
    - Architecture Jobs - Lake St Houses and Apartments, Newburgh, NY, 1971 (Folder 8.8)
    - Architecture Jobs - Lakeview Arms Apartments, Poughkeepsie, NY, 1989 (Folder 8.9)
    - Architecture Jobs - Mt. Zion Baptist Church, 1989, 1995 (Folder 8.10)
    - Architecture Jobs - "Neighborhood rehabilitation", 1991 (Folder 8.11)
    - Architecture Jobs - St. Anna Apartments, Poughkeepsie, NY, 1998 (Folder 8.12)
    - Architecture Jobs - St. John's Lutheran Church, 1992 (Folder 8.13)
    - Architecture Jobs - St. Simeon Senior Apartments II, 1992 (Folder 8.14)
    - Architecture Jobs - Vassar College, Intercultural Center (Jeh V. Johnson ALANA Center), 1992 (Folder 8.15)
    - Architecture Jobs - Whitney Young Manor Apartments, Yonkers, circa 1980 (Folder 8.16)
    - Architecture Jobs - Unidentified buildings, 1987-1988 (Folder 8.17)
    - Cars (for Classic Car Magazine 8/10), [2010?] (Folder 8.18)
    - Europe, undated (Folder 8.19)
    - Fisk University buildings, undated (Folder 8.20)
    - Fisk University, President's House, 1985-1986 (Folder 8.21)
    - Johnson, Jeh V., 1979 (Folder 8.22)
    - Johnson, Jeh V. - High school reunions, 1982-1999 (Folder 8.23)
    - Johnson, Jeh V. - Judging student model home contest, 1974 (Folder 8.24)
    - Johnson, Jeh V. with Max Bond, 1956, 1968, undated (Folder 8.25)
    - Johnson, Jeh V. with others, undated (Folder 8.26)
    - [Johnson, Norma Edelin?], circa 1955 (Folder 8.27)
    - NCARB - People, 1996, undated (Folder 8.28)
    - New York Tech Annual Competition, 1980 (Folder 8.29)
    - Office picnic, 1995 (Folder 8.30)
    - Vassar College, 2000 (Folder 8.31)
    - Vassar College - Architecture student projects, circa 1974, 1998 (Folder 8.32)
    - Vassar College - Architecture students, circa 1966-1968 (Folder 8.33)
    - Vassar College - Architecture students, 1969 (Folder 8.34)
    - Vassar College - Architecture students, 1971, 1975 (Folder 8.35)
    - Vassar College - Architecture students, 1976-1979 (Folder 8.36)
    - Vassar College - Architecture students, 1981-1982 (Folder 8.37)
    - Vassar College - Architecture students, circa 1983 - circa 1984 (Folder 8.38)
    - Vassar College - Architecture students, 1984 - circa 1986 (Folder 8.39)
    - Vassar College - Architecture students, 1987-1990 (Folder 8.40)
    - Vassar College - Architecture students, 1991-1994 (Folder 8.41)
    - Vassar College - Architecture students, circa 1990s (Folder 8.42)
    - Vassar College - Architecture students, 1994-1995 (Folder 8.43)
    - Vassar College - Architecture students, 1996-1998 (Folder 8.44)
    - Vassar College - Architecture students, 1999 (Folder 8.45)
    - Vassar College - Architecture students, 2000-2001 (Folder 8.46)
    - Unidentified, undated (Folder 8.47)
    - Unidentified buildings, undated (Folder 8.48)
  - Slides
    - Architectural Renderings, 1986-1989 (Folder 8.49)
    - Architecture Jobs - Apartments, 1978-1989 (Folder 8.50)
    - Architecture Jobs - Churches, 1971-1992 (Folder 8.51)
    - Architecture Jobs - Commonwealth Drive Apartments, 1973 (Folder 8.52)
    - Architecture Jobs - Dutchess County Mental Health Center, 1970 (Folder 8.53)
    - Architecture Jobs - Edith Macy Conference Center, 1985 (Folder 8.54)
    - Architecture Jobs - Harriet Tubman Apartments, 1978 (Folder 8.55)
    - Architecture Jobs - LaGrange town hall, 1968-1971 (Folder 8.56)
    - Architecture Jobs - Lake St Houses and Apartments, Newburgh, NY, 1971-1982 (Folder 8.57)
    - Architecture Jobs - Medical Offices, 1978-1984 (Folder 8.58)
    - Architecture Jobs - Miscellaneous buildings, 1964-1997, undated (Folder 8.59)
    - Architecture Jobs - St. Simeon Senior Apartments, 1972 (Folder 8.60)
    - Architecture Jobs - St. Simeon Senior Apartments II, 1992 (Folder 8.61)
    - Architecture Jobs - Vassar College, Intercultural Center (Jeh V. Johnson ALANA Center), 1993 (Folder 8.62)
    - Architecture Jobs - YMCA, 1969-1983 (Folder 8.63)
    - Buildings, 1978, 1987 (Folder 8.64)
    - Churches, 1959-2004, undated (Folders 8.65-8.66)
    - Gindele & Johnson offices, 1968-1978 (Folder 8.67)
    - Reference - American houses (Non-Dutchess County), 1969-1993 (Folder 8.68)
    - Reference - Dutchess County, 1968-1994 (Folder 8.69)
    - Reference - Historical building examples, 1977-1995 (Folder 8.70)
    - Reference - Jeh V. Johnson buildings, 1960 (Folder 8.71)
    - Travel (Paris, Great Britain, [Tunis?], [NC?]), 1959 (Folder 9.1)
    - Travel (California and the Pacific Northwest), 1982 Jul (Folder 9.2)
    - Travel (California, Massachusetts, Texas, Utah), 1985 Mar-Aug (Folder 9.3)
    - Travel (Mesa Verde, Colorado Desert, St. Louis), 1987 Jul-Aug (Folder 9.4)
    - Travel, 1988 Jun-Sep (Folder 9.5)
    - Travel, 1989 Jul-Aug (Folder 9.6)
    - Travel, 1989-1991 (Folder 9.7)
    - Travel (Niagara Falls), 1994 (Folder 9.8)
    - Travel and family, 1994 (Folder 9.9)
    - Travel (Europe, Paris), 1995 (Folder 9.10)
    - Travel and family, 1995 (Folder 9.11)
    - Travel (Europe), 1996 (Folder 9.12)
    - Travel (Spain), 1996 (Folder 9.13)
    - Travel, 1996-1997 (Folder 9.14)
    - Travel (Southern U.S.), 1997 (Folder 9.15)
    - Travel (Alaska), 1998 (Folder 9.16)
    - Travel, 1998-2000 (Folder 9.17)
    - Travel (Europe), 1999 (Folder 9.18)
    - Travel (Italy), 1999 Aug (Folder 9.19)
    - Travel (Colorado and Arizona), 2000 (Folder 9.20)
    - Travel (Europe), [2001?] (Folder 9.21)
    - Travel (Italy), 2003 (Folder 9.22)
    - Travel and family, 2006-2007 (Folder 9.23)
- Series VIII. Audio Reels, 1962, undated
  - "Thurgood Marshall", undated (Folder 9.24)
  - Unidentified, 1962 (Folder 9.25)
  - Unidentified, undated (Folder 9.26)
  - Unidentified, undated (Folder 9.27)
- Series IX. Plans, 1950-2005
  - Churches, 1970-2003; [12 roll boxes]
    - Bethel Missionary Baptist Church (Wappingers Falls, NY), 1984-1997 (Roll Box 1)
    - Beulah Baptist Church and Sunday School Building (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1986-2003 (Roll Box 2)
    - Central Baptist Church (Salt Point, NY), 1987 (Roll Box 3)
    - Ebenezer Baptist Church (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1995; [4 boxes] (Roll Boxes 4-7)
    - Mount Zion Baptist Church (Greenhaven, NY), 1995; [2 boxes] (Roll Boxes 8-9)
    - Mount Zion Baptist Church (Portchester, NY), 1984-1986 (Roll Box 10)
    - Riverview Missionary Baptist Church, tracings and prints (Kingston, NY), 1995-1996 (Roll Box 11)
    - Saint Clara Church (Kingston, NY, undated (Roll Box 1)
    - Salvation and Praise Deliverance Center (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1998 (Box 14 (Oversize))
    - Varick Memorial AME Zion Church (Brooklyn, NY), 1976 (Roll Box 12)
    - Vassar Temple, 1995-1996 (Roll Box 107)
    - Miscellaneous Churches, 1970-1992 (Roll Box 1)
  - Commercial and Community Buildings, 1956-2005; [37 roll boxes]
    - 7 Fulton Court (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1994 (Roll Box 13)
    - Bardavon Theater Building (Poughkeepsie, NY, undated (Roll Box 13)
    - Beacon Shopping Center - Victor Looper (Beacon, NY), 1973; [Over 28-inch roll] (Roll Box 126 (Oversize))
    - Chelsea Homes, Inc. - Tanglewood Motel (Marlboro, NY), 1988 (Roll Box 13)
    - Day Treatment Center (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1982 (Roll Box 13)
    - Dutchess Community College, Drumlin Cafeteria (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1971 (Roll Box 14)
    - Dutchess Community College, Drumlin Cafeteria (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1974; [Over 28-inch roll] (Roll Box 126 (Oversize))
    - Dutchess County Mental Health Center (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1967; [Over 36-inch roll; 2 boxes] (Roll Boxes 128-129 (Oversize))
    - Dutchess Design and Development, Proposed Warehouse Extension (Lagrange, NY), 1979 (Roll Box 13)
    - East End Engine Company (New Hamburg, NY), 1980-1981; [2 boxes] (Roll Boxes 15-16)
    - New Hamburg Fire District (New Hamburg, NY), 1956-1960 (Roll Box 16)
    - Elementary School (Highland, NY), 1968 (Roll Box 17)
    - Eleanor Roosevelt Center at Val-Kill (ERVK) - Garage Stable Building (Hyde Park, NY), 1998-2000 (Roll Box 17)
    - Fisk University, "The Humanities Center" (Jeh V. Johnson Columbia Thesis) (Nashville, TN), 1958 May (Roll Box 43)
    - Fisk University, "The Humanities Center" (Jeh V. Johnson Columbia Thesis) (Nashville, TN), 1958; [5 oversize boards] (Map Case - Drawer 35)
    - Fulton Ave Medical Building (Poughkeepsie, NY, undated (Roll Box 17)
    - Girl Scouts of the USA (GSUSA) - The Camp of Tomorrow, Edith Macy Conference Center (Mount Pleasant, NY), 1985-1987; [5 boxes] (Roll Boxes 18-22)
    - Girl Scouts of the USA (GSUSA) - The Camp of Tomorrow, Edith Macy Conference Center (Mount Pleasant, NY), 1985; [Over 36-inch roll] (Roll Box 127 (Oversize))
    - IBM Facility, Saw Mill River Road ((Mount Pleasant, NY?)), 1984 (Roll Box 17)
    - IBM Hangar Rehabilitation / Hudson Valley Regional Airport (Wappingers Falls, NY), 1983; [2 boxes] (Roll Boxes 23-24)
    - Jetco Facilities (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1965 (Roll Box 25)
    - The Lincoln Center (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1970 (Roll Box 17)
    - The New Catherine Street Community Center, originals and prints (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1975-1978; [3 boxes] (Roll Boxes 26-28)
    - New Masonic Lodge, Progressive Lodge No. 64, 245 S 11th Ave (Mount Vernon, NY), 1969 (Roll Box 17)
    - Newburgh-Beacon Bridge Toll (Beacon, NY), 1977-1979; [2 boxes] (Roll Boxes 29-30)
    - Offices - Berman, Dr. Donald (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1981 (Roll Box 31)
    - Offices - Doley, Harold (New Orleans, LA), 2002 (Roll Box 31)
    - Offices - Economou, Jack, 1980 (Roll Box 31)
    - Offices - Edelin, Dr. Kenneth, 1977 (Roll Box 31)
    - Offices - Fischman, Dr. Alan (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1981 (Roll Box 31)
    - Offices - Gold, Burton (Poughkeepsie, NY), 2002 (Roll Box 31)
    - Offices - Scenic Hudson Inc., One Civic Center Plaza (Poughkeepsie, NY), 2002 (Roll Box 31)
    - Offices - Sugg, E.M., 260 New Hackensack Rd (Wappingers Falls, NY), 1976-1981 (Roll Box 32)
    - Offices - Urban League of Westchester (Mount Vernon, NY), 1971 (Roll Box 31)
    - Offices and Medical Building for Salvenitz and Lieberman, 1973-1974 (Roll Box 33)
    - Pathmark Supermarket / Bedford-Stuyvesant Commercial Center, Brooklyn (New York, NY), 1976-1978; [Over 28-inch roll; 2 boxes] (Roll Boxes 116-117)
    - Peg Leg Bates Country Club (Kerhonkson, NY), 1981-1983 (Roll Box 31)
    - Planned Parenthood of the Mid-Hudson Valley Offices and Clinic, 14 Prince St (Monticello, NY), 2001 (Roll Box 34)
    - Planned Parenthood Offices and Clinic, 178-182 Church St / 17 Noxon St (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1984-2005 (Roll Box 35)
    - Planned Parenthood Offices and Clinic, 395 Main St (Beacon, NY), 1999-2001 (Roll Box 34)
    - Planned Parenthood Offices and Clinic, 44 North Chestnut St (New Paltz, NY), 1998-1999 (Roll Box 36)
    - Poughkeepsie Tennis Club (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1960-1965 (Roll Box 37)
    - Prince Hall Grand Lodge (New York, NY), 1978 (Roll Box 38)
    - Proposed Shopping Center (Dover Plains, NY), 1975-1976 (Roll Box 39)
    - Queen City Mall (Poughkeespie, NY), 1973; [3 boxes] (Roll Boxes 40-42)
    - Rhinebeck Country School (Rhinebeck, NY), 1975-1976 (Roll Box 39)
    - SCORE Project - The West Strand (Kingston, NY), 1977 (Roll Box 77)
    - SCORE Project - The West Strand / Forst Packing Company Building (Kingston, NY), 1980; [Over 36-inch roll] (Roll Box 130 (Oversize))
    - Shopping Center (Kingston, NY), 1981 (Roll Box 39)
    - Supermarket (Kerhonkson, NY), 1990 (Roll Box 39)
    - Taylor Manufacturing Co. Addition (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1974 (Roll Box 39)
    - Turnkey Development Company (Boston, MA), 1970; [Over 36-inch roll] (Roll Box 132 (Oversize))
    - Turnkey Development Company (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1970; [Over 36-inch roll] (Roll Box 132 (Oversize))
    - Villa Lewaro, Carriage House (Irvington, NY), 1995-1998 (Roll Box 43)
    - Whitney M. Young, Jr. Health Center (Albany, NY), 1972 (Roll Box 44)
    - Whitney M. Young, Jr. Health Center (Albany, NY), 1972; [Over 28-inch roll] (Roll Box 126 (Oversize))
    - YMCA (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1967 (Roll Box 43)
  - Multi-Unit Residences, 1950-2003; [58 roll boxes]
    - 22 Fallkill Ave (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1996 (Roll Box 45)
    - 55 South Hamilton St (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1986-1992 (Roll Box 45)
    - 125 Saint Paul St (Brookline, MA), 1980-1981 (Roll Box 46)
    - 140-144 Smith St Duplexes (Poughkeepsie, NY), 1987-1990 (Roll Box 45)
    - 145 Main St (Beacon, NY), 1987-1988 (Roll Box 45)
    - 238-240 Grand St (Newburgh, NY), 1976 (Roll Box 46)
    - The Academy Mews Condominiums, 154 Academy St (Poughkeespie, NY), 1981-1982 (Roll Box 86)
    - The Academy Mews Condominiums, 154 Academy St (Poughkeespie, NY), 1981-1982; [Over 36-inch roll] (Roll Box 133 (Oversize))